这些基于图像的视觉控制策略有两个重要的要求。
These image based visual control strategies have got two important requirements.
一种是可靠地找到目标对象上的点，并且可靠地表示每一个点
One is to reliably find the points on the target object, and by reliably means every
单帧：当物体移动或相机移动时，我们需要能够识别
single frame: as the object is moving or the camera is moving, we need to be able to identify
目标对象上的相同点。
the same points on the target object.
第二个问题是确定哪个点是哪个。这就是我们所说的通信
The second problem is to determine which point is which. This is what we call the correspondence
问题。因此，在我们之前的三角形目标的情况下，我们需要确定哪个
problem. So, in the case of our triangular target before, we need to determine which
当前视图中的点对应于所需视图中的哪个点。
point in the current view corresponds to which point in the desired view.
现在考虑第一个问题：我们如何可靠地找到目标对象上的点。
Considering now the first problem: how do we reliably find points on the target object.
曾几何时，这是通过创造非常高的人造场景来完成的
Once upon a time this was done by creating artificial scenes that have got very high
形成鲜明对比。所以这是我在20世纪90年代的博士研究中的两个例子，以及我的观点
contrasts. So here are two examples from my PhD research back in the 1990s, and what I
曾经是一个黑色的背景和一个白色的物体。所以我们可以使用非常简单
had was very much a black background and a white object. So we could use very simple
阈值技术和二进制视觉处理技术非常非常
thresholding techniques and binary vision processing techniques, which were very very
快，以便识别对象。但这显然是非常不现实的。
fast, in order to identify the object. But this is, clearly, very unrealistic.
另一种方法是在具有独特性的场景中引入一些东西
Another approach is to introduce something into the scene which has got a distinctive
颜色。我们之前已经谈过这个移动机器人如何相对于导航
color. We have talked before about how this mobile robot could navigate with respect to
橙色交通锥。右侧的图像显示了我们的室内飞行着陆目标
an orange traffic cone. The image on the right shows our landing target for an indoor flying
机器人。它可以看到这四个黄色目标的配置，识别质心
robot. It could see this configuration of four yellow targets, identify the centroid
那些，并落在他们身上。
of those, and land on them.
我们能够轻松解决问题的另一种方法是使目标变得非常明亮;
Another way we can make the problem easy is to make the target something that's very bright;
实际发光的东西。所以也许我们可以在物体上放置彩色LED
something that actually emits light. So perhaps we could put a colored LED on the object in
现场，机器人的视觉系统可以识别非常明亮的特定斑块
the scene, and the robot's vision system can identify that particular patch of very bright
颜色。通过使用明亮的颜色，它更容易分割。
color. By using the bright color it makes it easier to segment.
另一种方法是在对象上放置某种模式，这里我们看到了一些
Another approach is to put some kind of pattern on the object, and here we see a number of
用于本地化的模式。在中间我们有我们称之为自我相似的东西
patterns that are used for localisation. In the middle we have what we call a self-similar
具有里程碑意义，你可以看到计算机视觉算法能够非常非常强大
landmark, and you can see that the computer vision algorithm is able to very, very robustly
确定这三个地标中心的位置，几乎与此无关
determine the position of the centres of those three landmarks, almost irrespective of the
即使目标有些模糊，也可以使用工作表的姿势。在左边我们看到一些
pose of the sheet, even if the targets are somewhat obscured. On the left we see some
相关的地标，这次使用的是垂直线而不是圆形
related landmarks, this time using vertical lines rather than circles, which are used
在那个特定的机器人中，识别坩埚到机器人的位置，以便它可以捡起它。
in that particular robot to identify the location of the crucible to the robot so it can pick it up.
我们也可以使用右侧所示的QR码。我们可以计算QR码的质心，
We can also use QR code as shown here on the right. We can compute centroid of the QR code,
它是一种非常独特的模式，但QR码还包含许多字节的信息。
it’s a very unique pattern, but the QR code also contains a number of bytes of information.
通常这些用于在广告中编码URL。所以这个QR码有一个
Often times these are used to encode URLs in advertising. So this QR code has got a
位置，但它也有一些与之相关的信息。
position but it's also got some information associated with it.
与QR码相关的是另一种称为AR代码或增强现实的代码
Related to QR codes is another type of code called an AR code or an augmented reality
代码，它们可用于标记三维世界中的对象。
code, and they can be used to label objects in a three-dimensional world.